{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937104005","data":{"timestamp":" 946937104004"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937106103","data":{"timestamp":" 946937106102"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937108255","data":{"timestamp":" 946937108255"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937111484","data":{"timestamp":" 946937111484"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937113698","data":{"timestamp":" 946937113697"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937115932","data":{"timestamp":" 946937115931"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937118819","data":{"timestamp":" 946937118818"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937120975","data":{"timestamp":" 946937120975"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937123181","data":{"timestamp":" 946937123181"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937126441","data":{"timestamp":" 946937126440"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937128510","data":{"timestamp":" 946937128509"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937130586","data":{"timestamp":" 946937130586"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937133483","data":{"timestamp":" 946937133483"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937135679","data":{"timestamp":" 946937135679"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937137884","data":{"timestamp":" 946937137884"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937140942","data":{"timestamp":" 946937140941"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937143292","data":{"timestamp":" 946937143292"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937145616","data":{"timestamp":" 946937145615"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937148693","data":{"timestamp":" 946937148692"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937150825","data":{"timestamp":" 946937150825"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937152958","data":{"timestamp":" 946937152957"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937156005","data":{"timestamp":" 946937156005"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937158148","data":{"timestamp":" 946937158148"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937160264","data":{"timestamp":" 946937160264"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937163397","data":{"timestamp":" 946937163396"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937165827","data":{"timestamp":" 946937165826"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937168251","data":{"timestamp":" 946937168250"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937171428","data":{"timestamp":" 946937171428"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937173704","data":{"timestamp":" 946937173703"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937175953","data":{"timestamp":" 946937175952"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937178881","data":{"timestamp":" 946937178881"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937181076","data":{"timestamp":" 946937181076"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937183236","data":{"timestamp":" 946937183235"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937186096","data":{"timestamp":" 946937186096"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937188395","data":{"timestamp":" 946937188395"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937190730","data":{"timestamp":" 946937190728"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937193859","data":{"timestamp":" 946937193858"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937196261","data":{"timestamp":" 946937196261"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937198666","data":{"timestamp":" 946937198666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937201645","data":{"timestamp":" 946937201645"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937203885","data":{"timestamp":" 946937203884"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937206168","data":{"timestamp":" 946937206167"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937209413","data":{"timestamp":" 946937209413"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937211699","data":{"timestamp":" 946937211698"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937213983","data":{"timestamp":" 946937213982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937217283","data":{"timestamp":" 946937217283"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937219716","data":{"timestamp":" 946937219715"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937222186","data":{"timestamp":" 946937222185"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937224982","data":{"timestamp":" 946937224982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937227150","data":{"timestamp":" 946937227149"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937229312","data":{"timestamp":" 946937229312"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937232741","data":{"timestamp":" 946937232741"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937235097","data":{"timestamp":" 946937235097"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937237446","data":{"timestamp":" 946937237446"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937240543","data":{"timestamp":" 946937240542"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937242801","data":{"timestamp":" 946937242800"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937245091","data":{"timestamp":" 946937245091"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937248076","data":{"timestamp":" 946937248075"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937250206","data":{"timestamp":" 946937250205"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937252334","data":{"timestamp":" 946937252334"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937255365","data":{"timestamp":" 946937255365"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937257543","data":{"timestamp":" 946937257543"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937259732","data":{"timestamp":" 946937259731"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937262870","data":{"timestamp":" 946937262870"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937265047","data":{"timestamp":" 946937265046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937267240","data":{"timestamp":" 946937267239"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937270448","data":{"timestamp":" 946937270447"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937272787","data":{"timestamp":" 946937272787"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937275060","data":{"timestamp":" 946937275059"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937275872","data":{"timestamp":" 946937275871"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937275948","data":{"timestamp":" 946937275948"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937297917","data":{"timestamp":" 946937297917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" ab2fd61a-a1bb-4f56-be01-59ad8e4822ad"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937297980","data":{"timestamp":" 946937297980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" fc08648d-e557-474a-93af-293568665060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937327851","data":{"timestamp":" 946937327851"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" fc08648d-e557-474a-93af-293568665060"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937333172","data":{"timestamp":" 946937333172"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 11009533-69f9-4d6c-8100-76f373c7b717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937346400","data":{"timestamp":" 946937346400"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 11009533-69f9-4d6c-8100-76f373c7b717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937348864","data":{"timestamp":" 946937348863"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 11009533-69f9-4d6c-8100-76f373c7b717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937349021","data":{"timestamp":" 946937349021"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 11009533-69f9-4d6c-8100-76f373c7b717"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_3"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937361749","data":{"timestamp":" 946937361749"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 705066e7-0563-4e53-95c2-70a7b3526d54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_W-E-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937387057","data":{"timestamp":" 946937387056"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 705066e7-0563-4e53-95c2-70a7b3526d54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_E_W-E-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937413864","data":{"timestamp":" 946937413864"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 705066e7-0563-4e53-95c2-70a7b3526d54"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_E_W-E-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946937413930","data":{"timestamp":" 946937413930"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_010448"," gameId":" 349bdbe8-12a1-4996-b0b1-d01a1cf490b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Usiku mmoja Sungura alimtembelea Jimbi na familia yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIMBI"," userResponse":" JIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}